# rameşaliyev

**Senior Software Engineer** 

I'm an experienced software engineer in the web development field. But I'm mostly curious about what I don't know. For the past few years, I'm attending university to have a strong grasp of computer science and become good at math to achieve my new goals. Which is Machine Learning and Data Science.

### experiences

Senior Full Stack Developer @ OmmaSign Sep 2018 - Present

Senior Frontend Developer @ Pisano Feb 2018 - Sep 2018 (8 months)

Co-Founder & Full Stack Developer @ Ecma Co. Ltd. Jun 2017 - Feb 2018 (9 months)

Lead Full Stack Developer @ Emlakjet Jan 2016 - Oct 2017 (1 year 10 months)

Senior JavaScript Developer (Consultant) @ Turkcell Oct 2013 - Dec 2015 (2 years 3 months)

JavaScript Developer @ E-NET Internet Technology Co. Jan 2013 - Sep 2013 (9 months)

Frontend Developer @ Techpoint Labs Mar 2012 - Jan 2013 (11 months)

Full Stack Developer @ Koridor Design Studio Feb 2009 - Mar 2012 (3 years 2 months)

#### education

Yildiz Technical University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Engineering (2018 - 2022)

Sakarya University
Associate of Science - AS, Computer Programming (2016 - 2018)

Zeytinburnu Industrial Vocational High School High School Diploma, Electronics (2004 - 2007)

# volunteer experience

Instructor @ Frontend Camp'17 Summer Aug 2017

Organiser / Speaker @ JSNinjas - Free For All Aug 2015

Speaker @ The Frontiers:Mini Jun 2015

## links

ramesaliyev.com github.com/ramesaliyev linkedin.com/in/ramesaliyev twitter.com/ramesaliyev

### contact

creator@ramesaliyev.com